WARNING! The footage you are about to watch is of a sensitive nature
and although it may not be suitable for all viewers, it is for the glory of God.
This woman has come to The SCOAN suffering from a cruel skin disease,
which has afflicted her entire body.
Her skin has become so sensitive that it flakes and peels off at the slightest touch,
rendering her unable to wear clothing.
She is a young lady, at only 25 years old but outwardly no one would know.
Disfigured by the brutal affliction, the skin all over her body has been affected
by this destructive skin disease.
Even her lips have become bright red, being raw and blistered by the delibitating ailment.
The skin looks as if it is slowly melting.
How can she talk, eat or have any form of normality in her life?
Just imagine the torment, agony and pain.
Let alone the shame and embarrassment such an ailment would bring.
WATCH INSTANT HEALING!!!
The skin has become like scales, cracked and broken up into pieces,
which then become dry, and either flake or peel off.
It is a gruesome sight and difficult to behold.
As we continue to watch, we clearly see that no place has been left untouched
by this ruthless and aggressive skin disease.
She is living a life of constant, unending pain.
Viewers, for a moment put yourself in her position
and imagine what life would be like in such a condition.
It is beyond what mere words can adequately describe.
Mrs Bose Stephen has come to The SCOAN, knowing that her case has gone beyond the power of nature.
Her sickness has gone beyond medical explanation and treatment.
It has become a curse and therefore requires divine intervention.
Who else can remove the curse but God.
Who else can justly do it.
It is non other than our Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ.
By His death on the cross, Jesus broke the curse of sin and death that we deserve.
He purchased healing for us at the price of great suffering.
It is Christ's victory that gives us victory.
And it is a product of this victory that Mrs Stephen has come to The SCOAN to receive.
My name is Maria Ibukun.
The sister sitting beside you, who is she to you?
She is my sister from the same mother and father.
Tell us her name and her age.
Mrs Bose Stephen, 25 years old.
And she is your biological sister?
Yes.
Can you tell us what the problem is that brought her to The SCOAN today?
Body poison.
She cannot eat, sit down, stand, sleep or talk.
She does not feel like talking because of this body poison?
Yes.
We went to hospital. We have been at the hospital for a long time.
I believe that God will do a miracle in her life today to heal her.
We pray with you that Jesus, God Almighty, will set her free today, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
WATCH INSTANT HEALING!!!
HEALING TIME
In the mighty name of Jesus! In the blood of Jesus Christ!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer in Jesus‘ Name
There is spiritual transformation.
You don’t need to be told that this woman cannot sleep, cannot do anything on her own
but right now you can see the power of God Almighty has set her free.
Look at her right now. Walking confidently and now she can be touched
but before now no one could touch her.
Look at what is coming out of the woman!
Look at the screen of the television! This is the substance of the poison.
This is the power of God.
This is marvellous, this is glorious, this is wonderful.
Vomiting Poisonous and Bloody Substances
In excruciating pain and burning sensation all over her.
She was having loss of strength, loss of appetite, along other forms of symptoms
due to this terrible problem of body poison in her life.
That is the internal one.
The external one is the one you can see.
But the internal one – that is the one Jesus removed in your presence.
Thank You, Jesus!
My wife is healed! I am happy now.
I can talk now. Before now, I could not talk.
After the man of God prayed for me, I can talk.
Praise the Lord!
My name is Bose Stephen.
The sickness I had was body poison.
My body used to itch.
After the man of God prayed for me, my body does not itch anymore.
I could not talk but after the man of God prayed for me, I can talk.
Praise the Lord!
My body was hot but after the man of God prayed for me,
it was not hot anymore and I vomited all this.
Praise the Lord!
I will sin no more.
My name is Stephen. This is my wife.
The problem that brought us here was body poison.
My wife was poisoned.
She could not eat, talk and felt hot but now, she can talk.
After the man of God prayed for her, she vomited all the poison.
Praise the Lord!
Poisonous and Bloody Substances Vomited by Mrs Bose Stephen
I thank God for healing me. I can talk now.
I am very strong now.
Thank You, Jesus!
Mrs Bose Stephen Able to Wear Clothes After the Prayer of Prophet T.B. Joshua
Hallelujah!
Immediately after the prayer of Prophet T.B. Joshua in Jesus Christ’ name,
Mrs Bose Stephen was able to wear her clothing.
Evidence of the miraculous transformation that has occurred in her life.
Mrs Bose Stephen Able to Wear Clothes After the Prayer of Prophet T.B. Joshua
Before and After
Yeah!
I am healed!
I am saved!
I am redeemed!
Born again!
Hallelujah!
I am saved, in Jesus' name!
I am redeemed, in Jesus' name!
Hallelujah!
In Jesus' name, demons flee!
In the name of Jesus, I have been set free!
In Jesus' name, I have been saved!
In Jesus' name, I have been delivered!
Glory glory!
Hallelujah!
My name is Bose Stephen.
The resurrection power of God has flowed into her body
and washed away all the sickness and disease. All glory be to God!
TESTIMONY TIME
Mrs Bose Stephen Testifying Amidst Visitors to The SCOAN
This is Pastor Harry from Rotterdam Christian Life Centre and Emmanuel Television.
I am here on this occasion in The SCOAN, Lagos, Nigeria.
All around me, I am surrounded by people from all over this globe.
We have people here from Australia, South Africa, United States, Canada,
Germany, Switzerland, Austria, from all over the globe and last but not least
we also have people here from the Netherlands.
Let us welcome our brothers and sisters who are watching this programme right now
on television, with a big clap offering. Let’s give Jesus a big clap offering.
Hallelujah!
My name is Bose Stephen.
What brought me here was body poison.
For so many years, we had gone to hospitals, native doctors
and many places but I couldn’t get cured.
But when I came to The SCOAN and the man of God stretched his hand
towards me, I received strength.
I started running! After running, when I stood, I vomited all the poison.
After some time, I felt so cold inside me.
Before and After
Then, I could not even talk or eat but when the man of God
stretched his hand towards me, I started eating.
Hallelujah!
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God’s power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives, Changing nations and Changing the world.
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 21/07/2018